http://www.sypherlaw.com/privacy-policy/

Call for a free consultation!
Contact
Call for a free consultation!
Privacy Policy Information Collection
Sypher Law collects two types of information: anonymous and personal information. Anonymous information, like your computer?s IP address, may be collected without your knowledge. Personal information, like your name and e-mail address, is always asked for outright before it is collected.
Information Usage
We use anonymous information for things like analyzing our site usage, monitoring site performance, and planning future parts of our site and its capabilities. We use personal information, like your name and e-mail address, to establish and confirm your identity and provide personalized information to you. We will not send you any non-personalized information unless you choose to opt-in.
Information Sharing
Sypher Law does not share personal information with any third party. Also, Sypher Law does not sell any information collected on our site to any third party.
Information Security
Sypher Law uses encryption, network design, and other tools and technologies to protect all information submitted to our site.
Legal Disclaimers
THE INFORMATION AND CONTENTS OF THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED AS IS.? IN NO WAY SHALL SYPHER LAW BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION DUE TO ACCESS OF, USE OF, OR INABILITY TO ACCESS THIS SITE OR ANY LINKED SITE.
THIS SITE MAY CONTAIN INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY MADE TO THE SITE AND ITS CONTENTS. SYPHER LAW DOES NOT WARRANT THIS SITE OR ITS CONTENTS IN ANY WAY; YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.
